Contact

8237680394 (Mobile) patilgaurav926@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/gauravmpatil (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

JavaScript

Python (Programming Language)

Languages

Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Marathi (Native or Bilingual)

English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Google - Technical Support Fundamentals

Google Cloud Platform
Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Google - Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User

Java

Honors-Awards

National Level Computer Knowledge Quiz

Scored Gold Badge in SQL Scored Gold Badge in Java

Gaurav Patil

Web Developer | Computer Engineer | Creator @ YouTube Thane

Summary

Experienced Blogger with a demonstrated history of working in the Computer and Network Security Industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), PHP, C, C++, Java, SQL, Ethical Hacking, Digital Marketing and Computer Security. Strong Operations Professional with a Bachelor of Engineering - BE focused in Computer Engineering from PVPPCOE | Padmabhushan Vasantdada Patil College of Engineering

Experience

YouTube
Ultra Spartans
April 2020 - Present (5 months)

Self Employed Web Developer June 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months) India

Education

PVPPCOE | Padmabhushan Vasantdada Patil College of Engineering

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineering · (2017 - 2020)

G.V.Acharya Polytechnic

Diploma, Computer Engineering · (2014 - 2017)

St. Anthony's Convent Higher Secondary School Class 10, SSC · (2011 - 2014)